Guide to the Seymour Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional Material, Accession 1982-M-010
  - ST. JOHN FAMILY, Series X
    - Correspondence
      - Clara Hitchcock (Seymour) St. John from
        - A-Z, 1884-1906, undated (Box 7, Folder 156)
        - Angel, Elizabeth Day (Seymour), 1898-1903 (Box 7, Folder 157)
        - Dean, Katherine Seymour (Parsons), 1900 (Box 7, Folder 158)
        - Edwards, Daisy DeForest, 1894, undated (Box 7, Folder 159)
        - Hitchcock, Charles Edward, 1891 (Box 7, Folder 160)
        - Hitchcock, Clara D., 1886, 1889 (Box 7, Folder 161)
        - Hitchcock, Clara Maria, 1889-1890, 1896 (Box 7, Folder 162)
        - Johnson, Marguerite, 1890 (Box 7, Folder 163)
        - Morris, Frances N., 1894-1906, undated (Box 7, Folder 164-166)
        - Scudder, Sylvia C., 1900, 1902 (Box 7, Folder 167)
        - Seymour, Charles (1843-1913), 1899, 1902 (Box 7, Folder 168)
        - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963), 1897-1899 (Box 7, Folder 169-170)
        - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963), 1909 (Box 7, Folder 171)
        - Seymour, Elizabeth (Day), 1890 (Box 7, Folder 172)
        - Seymour, Sarah (Hitchcock), 1897 September-1898 Jul, October-1899 December (Box 7, Folder 173-183)
        - Seymour, Sarah (Hitchcock), 1900 January-Jun, undated (Box 8, Folder 184-188)
        - Seymour, Thomas Day, 1897-1900 May, 1902 (Box 8, Folder 189-194)
        - "Cousin Abbie", 1890 (Box 8, Folder 195)
        - "Cousin Emma", 1890, undated (Box 8, Folder 196)
        - "Fannie W.", 1898-1901 (Box 8, Folder 197)
        - "Nita", 1894 (Box 8, Folder 198)
        - Unidentified, 1895-1901 (Box 8, Folder 199)
        - Envelopes with notes, 1895, 1899-1900 (Box 8, Folder 200)
      - Seymour St. John from
        - A-Z, 1928-1929 (Box 8, Folder 201)
        - Angel, Elizabeth Day (Seymour), 1928-1929 (Box 8, Folder 202)
        - Pease, Hoyt Curtiss, 1928-1929 (Box 8, Folder 203)
        - Pease, Polly, 1928-1929 (Box 8, Folder 204)
        - St. John, C. Wardell, 1928-1929 (Box 8, Folder 205)
        - St. John, Clara Hitchcock (Seymour), 1928-1929 (Box 8, Folder 206-207)
        - St. John, Francis, 1928-1929 (Box 8, Folder 208)
        - St. John, George (1877-), 1929 (Box 8, Folder 209)
        - St. John, George (1910-), 1928-1929, undated (Box 8, Folder 210-211)
        - "Grandmother" St. John, 1925, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 212)
        - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963), 1928 (Box 9, Folder 213)
        - Seymour, Charles (1912-1977), 1928 (Box 9, Folder 214)
        - Seymour, Gladys (Watkins), undated (Box 9, Folder 215)
        - "Aunt Addie," "Aunt Nell Cushman," "Aunt Nell" Seymour, 1928-1929 (Box 9, Folder 216)
        - "Jean", 1928-1929 (Box 9, Folder 217)
        - Miscellaneous and unidentified, 1928, undated (Box 9, Folder 218)
        - Cards, undated (Box 9, Folder 219)
        - Telegrams from mother and father, 1928-1929, undated (Box 9, Folder 220)
      - Bryn Mawr De Rebus Club: Clara Hitchcock (Seymour) St. John, 1899 October-1900 March (Box 9, Folder 221)
      - Bryn Mawr De Rebus Club: Sylvia C. Scudder, 1896, 1899-1900 (Box 9, Folder 222)
    - Writings
      - St. John, Clara Hitchcock (Seymour): "A Trip to the South", [ca. 1893] (Box 9, Folder 223)
      - St. John, Clara Hitchcock (Seymour): school papers, 1889, undated (Box 9, Folder 224)
      - "How Icebergs Are Formed", undated (Box 9, Folder 225)
      - Unidentified, undated (Box 9, Folder 226)
    - Personal and Miscellaneous
      - St. John, Clara Hitchcock (Seymour): Bryn Mawr course record, 1896-1900 (Box 9, Folder 227)
      - St. John, Clara Hitchcock (Seymour): memorabilia, 1897-1903, undated (Box 9, Folder 228-229)
      - St. John, Clara Hitchcock (Seymour): miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 230)
      - St. John, Seymour: miscellaneous, [ca. 1929] (Box 9, Folder 231)
    - Printed Material
      - St. John, Clara Hitchcock (Seymour); programs, menu, 1894, 1900, undated (Box 9, Folder 232)
      - St. John, Clara Hitchcock (Seymour): Bryn Mawr programs, 1900, undated (Box 9, Folder 233)
      - St. John, Clara Hitchcock (Seymour): Hillhouse High School programs, 1896 (Box 9, Folder 234)
      - Choate programs, 1930, undated (Box 9, Folder 235)
      - Miss Porter's School, 1904 (Box 9, Folder 236)
      - Clipping, undated (Box 9, Folder 237)
      - St. John, Seymour: tickets, labels, [ca. 1929] (Box 9, Folder 238)
      - L'Echo du Rosey, 1928-1929 (Box 10, Folder 239)
      - Newsclipping about Choate, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 240)
      - Theater and opera programs, 1928-1929 (Box 10, Folder 241)
      - Miscellaneous programs, 1929, undated (Box 10, Folder 242)
  - CHARLES SEYMOUR (1885-1963), Series XI
    - Correspondence
      - Charles Seymour (1885-1963) from
        - Angel, Elizabeth Day (Seymour), 1903-1909 (Box 10, Folder 243)
        - St. John, Clara Hitchcock (Seymour), 1906 (Box 10, Folder 244)
        - St. John, Clara Hitchcock (Seymour), 1908-1909 (Box 10, Folder 245-246)
        - Seymour, Sarah (Hitchcock), 1906 June-Aug, 1908-1909 (Box 10, Folder 247-249)
        - Seymour, Thomas Day, 1906 (Box 10, Folder 250)
        - Unidentified, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 251)
    - Writings
      - DeForest Prize essay, 1908 May 6 (Box 10, Folder 252)
  - PHOTOGRAPHS, Series XVIII
    - St. John family, unidentified, 1919, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 253)
    - Pictures taken by George St. John, Jr. at Cambridge, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 254)
    - Pictures taken by Clara (Seymour) St. John in France, [1929] (Box 10, Folder 255)
    - Seymour St. John: hockey, 1929 (Box 10, Folder 256)
    - Unidentified, [ca. 1928-1929] (Box 10, Folder 257)
    - Unidentified photographs - probably France and Switzerland, [ca. 1928-1929] (Box 10, Folder 258-259)